// Create an array containing all questions and answers.
    var quiz = [
        {question: "How many Legend of Zelda characters are in Super Smash Bros. Ultimate?",
        answers: ["9", "3", "4", "6"],
        correct: 3,
        correctGif: "<img src='assets/images/01-ssb-twoLinks.gif",
        wrongGif: "<img src='../images/wrong-ww-wave.gif' />"
        },

        {question: "What is the name of Link's faithful steed?",
        answers: ["Lorse", "Epona", "Shadowfax", "Zelda"],
        correct: 1,
        correctGif: "<img src='../images/02-tp-epona.gif />",
        wrongGif: "<img src='../images/wrong-ww-wave.gif' />"
        },

        {question: "What is the only game in the series where 5 pieces of heart make up a heart container, rather than 4?",
        answers: ["Twilight Princess", "Majora's Mask", "A Link Between Worlds", "Link's Awakening"],
        correct: 0,
        correctGif: "<img src='../images/03-la-heartPiece.gif />",
        wrongGif: "<img src='../images/wrong-ww-wave.gif' />"
        },

        {question: "What is the name of Link's recurring enemy, who looks like a monstrous pig?",
        answers: ["Gerudo", "Ahriman", "Ganon", "Vaati"],
        correct: 2,
        correctGif: "<img src='../images/04-alttp-ganon.gif />",
        wrongGif: "<img src='../images/wrong-ww-wave.gif' />"
        },

        {question: "What is the name of Princess Zelda's alter ego in The Wind Waker?",
        answers: ["Zolda", "Aryll", "Linkle", "Tetra"],
        correct: 3,
        correctGif: "<img src='../images/05-ww-tetra.gif />",
        wrongGif: "<img src='../images/wrong-ww-wave.gif' />"
        },
        
        {question: "What is the name of the final mask in Majora's Mask, that Link can only use during boss fights?",
        answers: ["The Fierce Deity", "The Wrathful God", "The Vengeful Spirit", "The Mask of Courage"],
        correct: 0,
        correctGif: "<img src='../images/06-hw-fierceDeity.gif />",
        wrongGif: "<img src='../images/wrong-ww-wave.gif' />"
        },

        {question: "Which of tollowing games does Link NOT appear in?",
        answers: ["Mario Kart 8", "Soulcalibur II", "Star Fox 64", "WarioWare Gold"],
        correct: 2,
        correctGif: "<img src='../images/07-mk8-linkBike.gif />",
        wrongGif: "<img src='../images/wrong-ww-wave.gif' />"
        },

        {question: "Which of the following is NOT a song in Ocarina of Time?",
        answers: ["Zelda's Lullaby", "Bolero of Fire", "Song of Storms", "Tempo of Time"],
        correct: 3,
        correctGif: "<img src='../images/08-oot-ocarina.gif />",
        wrongGif: "<img src='../images/wrong-ww-wave.gif' />"
        },

        {question: "What are the names of the two games released for the Game Boy Color that, when beat, could carry over to a third game/true ending?",
        answers: ["Link's Awakening & Link's Asleepening", "Spirit Tracks & The Phantom Hourglass", "Oracle of Ages & Oracle of Seasons", "Red Version & Blue Version"],
        correct: 2,
        correctGif: "<img src='../images/09-ooas-horse.gif />",
        wrongGif: "<img src='../images/wrong-ww-wave.gif' />"
        },

        {question: "Which of these is NOT one of the three stones you must retrieve in the first part of Ocarina of Time?",
        answers: ["Kokiri Emerald", "Goron Ruby", "Zora Sapphire", "Hylian Topaz"],
        correct: 3,
        correctGif: "<img src='../images/10-art-threeStones.gif />",
        wrongGif: "<img src='../images/wrong-ww-wave.gif' />"
        }
]

console.log(quiz[0].correct)
